Hello, everyone. I'm Haruka Kaki from Nor
izaka46.
This time, I'm going to play a game
called Don't Drop the Cake.
It's a game that was recently released,
and I thought it would be fun to play.
I wanted to try it, so I'm going to do
it, but where I'm shooting now is that I
'm going to do it for the first time in
the game broadcast room that I made with
the help of Sonepp-san around March.
This is the first time I'm doing a game
broadcast in a gaming room.
At that time, I also bought a green bag.
I'm wearing a green bag now.
This time, I'm going to carry a cake.
I want you to make it look like your
birthday.
I also celebrated my 25th birthday in
August.
I want you to celebrate it.
Thank you for the cake.
Thank you, thank you.
I don't know what's going on.
I always watch the completed video and
know.
Please do it.
I don't know much about it today.
I haven't done any research before
playing the game.
I don't know why I'm carrying a cake or
who it's for, but today I'm not the one
to celebrate, I'm the one to celebrate,
so I'd like to bring a cake to someone.
I'll do my best without dropping it.
If you drop a cake about this game, you
'll die.
I'm going to die.
This game is not for the cowardly.
Don't Drop the Cake is a horror game
where you carry a cake that shakes when
you walk and go through a space where
strange things and various traps await
you.
While balancing with your mouse so as not
to drop the cake, break through various
places full of fear.
Please see the end of the mystery answer
and the story of why you carry the cake.
Please watch until the end of the video.
I understand if I carry it to the end.
I see.
I will do it.
I can't clear it for the coward.
I got it.
I start a new game.
Don't drop the cake.
This is very easy.
This is a hard mode.
This is the speed of the enemy.
This is the size of the shaking of the
cake.
Well, let's go with normal for now.
Normal is the best.
Wait.
Here?
This?
This is the balance.
This is the front, left and right.
I should have cut my nails.
OK.
If you drop the cake, you will die.
Why?
Why? Do you really want to die?
Don't drop the cake and proceed.
It's true!
It's amazing!
Is it like that?
I just moved it a little and it moved a
lot.
Wait a minute.
It's difficult to carry a cake.
I haven't dropped a cake in my life yet.
And?
Ah!
I can look in different directions with
this.
I see.
Oh!
Cherry blossoms.
I felt Japan.
And what is this?
Good.
Here!
I'm not used to the operation.
This is...
Dangerous!
Cake...
Oh!
What?
Oh, something happened.
But I can't look down.
But this is...
It's like...
A little...
Just a little bit...
I've been looking at what kind of game it
is, but it seems to be surprising, so
everyone be careful.
I may be surprised if I look at it. When
I was in elementary school, I fell into a
trap with it.
Don't look for Wally. I got something.
No signal. It disappeared.
Oh, I see, it's like this, little by
little, don't look for Wally, I wonder
what it is, it's like a picture of
looking for Wally, please look for Wally
from here, there's something like that on
the Internet, and I'm a elementary school
student, I'm looking for it, I'm looking
for Wally, I'm looking for it, I'm
looking for it, I'm looking for it, I'm
looking for it, I'm looking
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry
It's dangerous. The cake is going to
fall.
I was surprised. It's not a cake.
It's dangerous. I'm a little surprised.
The cake is going to fall.
Leave it to me. That's what I'm good at.
Eh? Wait a minute.
Dangerous! Dangerous! Dangerous!
It's a lie, right?
This is dangerous!
Multitasking is difficult.
Dangerous!
What?
I'm sorry, but I died.
I'm sorry!
Wait a minute.
I didn't die even if I was threatened.
I didn't die even if it was delivered,
but I'm going to die here.
I'm a little bit of a beginner, but what
should I do?
Hey, wait a minute, it's hard.
Wait a minute, just push forward.
I just have to press the front button.
Cake, cake, cake.
I think it's good.
What?
Where am I trying to carry the cake?
It's dangerous.
A little more.
Something fell.
Wait a minute.
I didn't see it at all.
Something fell.
What happened?
It's dangerous.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it
's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's
coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's
coming, it's coming
That was a very technical way of dying.
What is this?
I'm sorry, I died.
What is this play right now?
It means that the flower was able to eat
the cake.
I didn't know that at all.
It's a little before.
The lock is F.
I think I was able to do it.
What is this room?
It's a sunflower.
Is that what it is?
What does this mean?
But the person earlier was also a flower.
I was told to run away from the hospital.
Do I have to run away from that person?
Should I go over there?
Oh, it's dangerous.
It's very difficult to do this while
trying not to drop the cake.
What should I do?
I'm not good at multitasking.
I'm not good at it.
Should I go in the direction of the
arrow?
What's going on?
Where did the person with the flower go?
I wonder if he's not there anymore.
The cake is dangerous.
Oh, I see.
That's it.
It's probably the one who has to press
the button in the room.
That's probably right.
Do I have to run while I go?
It's a little difficult.
Where did the person from earlier go?
Where is this?
Is this the room I entered?
Is this wrong?
No?
The cake is...
No, it's not.
Here.
Yes.
It's closed.
Please wait a moment.
Please come in a little further.
OK.
I closed the door and dropped it.
What is this place?
It's a house.
It seems that humans have become flowers.
It's like this.
I wonder where the person with the flower
was.
I'm in trouble.
What should I do?
Can I go there?
It's the same width, so I think I'll be
chased if I keep running away.
Is that okay?
I will definitely be chased.
I can't do that anymore.
I can't do this anymore.
Run as much as you can now.
I can go there.
I have a cake.
I was going to do this without changing
the height of my head, but I think I can
do it if I do something like running only
with my legs.
Wow, wait, which one is this?
Wow, wait, which one? What should I do?
Isn't it on the left here?
Oh, I'm frustrated. Where is this from?
This is from here.
Where is this from?
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know where I'm going, I don't
know where I'm going, I don't know where
I'm going, I don't know where I'm going,
I don't know where I'm going, I don't
know where I'm going, I don't know where
I'm going, I don't know where I'm going,
I don't know where I'm going, I don't
know where I'm going, I don't know where
I'm going, I don't know where I'm going,
I don't know where I'm going, I don't
know where I'm going, I don't know where
I'm going, I don't know where I'm going,
I don't know where I'm going, I don't
know where I'm going, I don't know where
I'm going, I don't know where I'm going,
I don't know where I'm going, I don't
know where I'm going, I don't know where
I'm going, I don't know where I'm going,
I don't know where I'm
I don't have anything here.
It was a garden where flowers were
blooming.
I want to build a house with a garden in
the future.
I want to be an old woman and live there
with flowers.
My grandmother grew a tree in the garden.
When I was at her house a while ago, she
said,
So I told her that Suzume-san is coming
to play with me.
She said that she doesn't see me that
much anymore in Osaka.
But she said that Suzume-san is coming to
play with me.
Sometimes my grandma sends me a picture
of Suzume.
It's cute, isn't it?
Here?
It's here!
Oops!
Hey!
Damn it!
I was kidding.
I was talking about my grandma's Suzume.
Where is the room?
I found it after I said there was only
one left.
This is where the cage is.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do when I think
about the cake.
Did I come here?
Is it here?
What is this place?
What about here?
Here?
Hm?
It's here!
Oh, I closed it.
It's here.
I'm looking at this.
Hmm.
There's a place like a house.
There's a place like a garden.
What is this?
It's like the daily life of flowers.
That's great.
Do your job.
I can't hear the footsteps anymore.
I'll come out.
I think I can do this.
I don't want to drop the cake here
anymore.
If I go there as it is, I can go.
But I don't know where it is.
I think I'm wearing good shoes.
I'm trying to wear good shoes.
But he must be a noble person in the way
he walks.
That person is like a manager.
I'm an intruder, so it's natural for me
to be eliminated.
I'm sorry.
I pushed the door.
I feel like I'm moving forward.
I think I'm on the next stage.
The stage has changed a little.
I feel like the door is far away.
Is it behind me?
Wait a minute!
Dangerous!
I have a way to escape!
Where?
I went too far.
A big car came out.
That's a big car too.
How is it?
I have a way to escape.
Isn't it there?
Is it a different place?
I made a mistake.
It's dangerous!
Can I go forward?
Can I go in?
I can go in!
What?
It's difficult.
I managed to do it.
Whose words are these?
It's amazing.
The atmosphere has changed.
I was very nervous.
I didn't expect an armadillo to get in
the way.
He is definitely the strongest in this
world.
It's definitely the strongest in the
That's right.
Moreover, it appears everywhere.
It's dangerous.
Be careful.
I understand.
What is this magatama talking about?
Even so.
You came all the way here with your hands
covered.
Really.
Can I be praised?
I don't think it's a shoki.
Thank you very much.
I'm doing my best to carry it.
Did you forget who I am?
There are people you have to meet, so I
helped you come to this world, right?
That's right. Then the person carrying
this is not from this world.
This is the world of the dead. I see.
I see.
It's a world where monsters are
everywhere.
Do you want to know what that monster is?
I want to know.
If you come here and it takes time, you
'll become a monster.
I see.
So he was originally a human being.
It would be nice if you could reach it
before your loved one is too late.
Then I have to go soon.
I see.
This person will deliver the cake to the
person he wants to meet.
This person is like a guide.
This person is the person I was talking
about earlier.
What should I do from here?
This is a dead end.
This person came to a completely
different place.
This person has nothing.
This person is cute.
It's cute.
Don't get close to me.
Why is it dangerous?
You can't eat the cake.
Don't give the cake to the main
character.
You can't eat this cake, can you?
I have a bad feeling about this.
I can't eat this cake anymore.
This is too scary.
You are dead.
What is that girl?
What is this place?
I've been dropping cakes in a place that
has nothing to do with it, but what
should I do?
I may be too bad at carrying cakes.
It's better to go to the wall and bend
it, so I'll do it.
But I shouldn't do that.
I learned this.
This is a TV factory.
This is like a production factory.
There is a cake here.
The cake!
If I could run, I would have wanted to
run for a long time.
It's dangerous.
The cake goes like this.
I'm going to die!
What should I do? Don't move me.
My friends from earlier.
Are these kids okay?
I didn't expect to be saved by these
guys.
It's true. I can drive this.
I see. You guys are originally...
You don't turn into monsters?
It's not a monster anymore, is it?
What's wrong?
It's not gay.
It's too gay.
Don't leave me alone.
Are you abandoning me so suddenly?
What was that?
I'm trying to get out of here.
Really?
Believe me.
I understand.
I got it.
Will you accept it like RAPIDA?
Don't worry, I'll take you to your
daughter.
Are you going to see your daughter?
This is your parents.
I'm going to the factory and run away.
Please proceed carefully.
I understand.
I'm going to see my daughter.
I have to deliver this cake to my
daughter.
I have to deliver it, but if I deliver
this kind of thing, it's like a cake
cover.
Oh, it's like the monster of the hand
that was said to be the strongest.
It's gone.
There's nothing.
What?
What? It's like this.
It's surprisingly kind.
The cake is dangerous.
What is it?
Who is it?
Be careful because the red light will
explode.
I got it.
I don't want to get hit.
I think I'll die if I get hit.
Is this okay?
I'm just walking in a straight line.
I'm sorry, I'm only looking at the cake.
I didn't notice it at all.
From here.
What?
You seem to like drawing.
Oh no.
What? What sound?
Up?
This girl is cute.
I'm going to die.
This is bad. I'm going to die.
Wait a minute.
Something is written.
Face character.
I see.
NICOCHAN is angry.
NICOCHAN.
I have to press this, right?
I'll press it.
Please wait.
Please wait a minute.
Can I press this?
Can I press it?
No, I can do it!
The next one is not angry.
What was it?
It's a normal face.
I understand my tendency.
I got it.
This is the first one to go this way,
then go that way, get angry, and then
die.
OK.
I don't think it's changed.
I'm sorry.
It shouldn't have changed.
It doesn't seem to change, so I'll keep
going this way and push it.
I'll go straight.
It wasn't straight.
I'll go this way and this way.
This is delicious.
This is correct.
I pressed the wrong button by mistake.
The cake is here at the end, isn't it?
This is delicious.
What were you?
The graffiti underneath this is the scene
of the incident, isn't it?
How did you get around that dead person?
You're a scary being with a cute face.
You can't underestimate it.
Cute looks are underestimated.
Oh, don't be crushed.
I got it.
It's dangerous.
All right.
I can do this.
I wanted to do this.
This is a long one.
I understand.
I will pick this up.
This is dangerous.
I will put the cake back in the middle.
This is dangerous, so I will look
carefully before I go.
What is this?
I see.
This is the one that tries to crush it
too much on the second floor.
This one is normal.
This one is fast.
This one will crush it twice.
This one is tall.
This is difficult.
Is this the same as before?
This is dangerous.
The cake is...
There is one more.
It's not coming down.
Is this okay?
This is dangerous.
Stop it.
I'm carrying the stage.
I'm here.
What is this place next?
The stage doesn't seem to have changed.
There is something here.
It's like a magician.
Did you get caught?
What is this sound?
It came from above.
What will happen?
What should I do?
What?
I was also trapped.
The worst phenomenon.
I have to run.
I hate it.
I don't want to be burned to death, but
if I go too far ahead, I'll bump into
this, so I can't go too far ahead.
I can't do this.
Cake, cake, cake.
Before that, the cake.
I'm the first, so wait a minute.
167 seconds left.
How much?
Oh, my God. What should I do?
Hey, stop it.
This is not the case.
Oh, my God.
Enter the factory computer and try to
stop the injury.
Thank you.
What are you? What kind of existence are
you?
Tell me before that.
I got it!
It's like...
What?
The existence inside the computer?
Is the existence inside the computer?
Oh no!
It's going to explode!
It's going to explode, so be careful.
I got it.
You told me earlier.
How is it?
Ah!
This is dangerous.
Who is playing this?
This is really...
It's too death game.
No!
Damn it!
Ah...
It's all over the place.
If I die on the way...
Ah!
Eh?
You are so kind.
I thought you would do it again in 210
seconds.
You are so kind.
Thank you very much for people like me.
You didn't touch the cake, did you?
It's been about a minute and a half.
It became very quiet.
There is something in it.
It's dangerous.
I made a mistake.
It's hot.
It's this way.
Damn it!
I think the next one is coming from the
right.
And then the next one.
It's the next one.
After this, I'll avoid it to the right.
This way.
I can't go any further.
I'll stop here.
Don't fall over here.
It was like a blueberry in yogurt.
I want everyone to see it.
It's just a little bit left.
I thought it was a little suspicious.
I thought it would be easy, but it seems
that it is difficult to hit it.
I think it will be difficult to hit it
again.
It's a blueberry.
I have 20 seconds left.
I have 10 seconds left.
It's too late.
It's over, so it's over.
I'm bugging you.
What is this sound?
It's 999 seconds.
The cake has been pierced.
This is cute.
I was in time.
Thank you.
I died a few times.
How many traps are there in this factory?
This is true.
What is this trap for?
Thank you.
See you again.
Is this okay here?
Is this the end of this stage?
It's not over yet.
This is still a factory.
But it's a little greenish, so I wonder
if it's a different place from here.
Isn't it blueberry now?
That monster has fast legs, but it seems
to have bad eyes.
If you enter the square, you may be able
to do it.
So if you are chased by three people, run
into the locker.
Run again? I'm a little bad at running
away.
What about here?
Where is this from?
I see.
It's a little dangerous if it's right in
front of you.
Did you press this?
It's dark.
What is this?
This is the place.
This rakuzaki is also cute.
These children are cute.
It's like slime.
I don't know where it's going.
I passed here.
I passed the gate.
There are many cakes here.
There is something here.
There is only one cake left.
Is it here?
It seems to be here.
I found it.
I don't want to drop the cake here.
I don't want to do it anymore.
These kids have been trapped for a long
time.
I feel sorry for them.
What's going to happen?
Can you open the door for me?
You're cute.
You're wearing a stylish hat.
That's good.
Can you go?
Can I go too?
Let's go.
Is this the end of the stage?
Oh, there's nothing here. I can live
without touching anything.
What is it?
Oh, it's not me.
It looks like the place I went through
earlier.
That magatama! Don't shoot me!
Don't shoot me!
Oh, it's a natural...
Oh, it's a beautiful place.
This is the first time I've seen him face
to face.
That's right. Nice to meet you.
This is the guide, Mokihwa.
I've been looking at it for a long time
here.
I can see it from here.
Using that machine.
I can't believe I put such a mechanical
thing in such a big nature.
If you use that, you can see most of the
world of the dead.
If you use it a little, you can
interfere.
That's why I've saved your life many
times.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Do you want me to tell you about this
world?
By the way, I haven't explained much
other than that your daughter is in this
world.
That's right.
All right, I'll tell you a little bit.
First of all, this is the world of the
dead.
Some of the people who died with Gideon
are wandering here.
When you come to this world, you will be
in a different form from before.
I'm not supposed to be like this. I was a
normal human being.
That's right. And if you spend time in
this world, you'll lose your reason.
I'm going to be a strange monster that
attacks others.
Hmm. I see. Then everyone was a human
being.
I've seen enough of how scary monsters
are.
I've seen it.
I did it.
The last thing I'm waiting for is...
It's the worst thing I've ever seen.
But there's only one way to live without
becoming a monster.
Oh.
It's to get rid of your past regrets
before you become a monster.
I see.
I have regrets, so I'm a little dizzy.
It makes me feel bad.
If you do that, you can disappear from
this world.
Disappear?
That's a little sad.
I'm sad, but I'm calling it an animal to
leave this world with a regret.
I don't know what's going to happen next.
I may be able to go to heaven.
Or I may be reborn as an ant and become a
person who carries food.
I think it's better to be a monster than
to be a monster.
I'm sure I'm living by forgetting who I
am.
I've forgotten who I am and I'm still
alive.
So I have to go see her as soon as
possible before she becomes a monster.
That's true.
But my daughter is here because she has
something left in her heart.
I wonder if that's this cake.
By the way, that cake.
Why are you holding it like that?
It's normal.
It's normal, but when I celebrate my
birthday in Nogizaka, I bring it with me
like this.
I'm not kidding.
There must have been other better ways.
There was a case where I put it in a box.
It can't be helped that you have to hold
the board with both hands.
The board you are using to replace the
cake tray has a special power.
I have a lot of power in me.
Really?
I put the cake in a box.
I think so.
I'm proud of it.
If my daughter brings this, it will be
awkward.
I'm proud of it.
I will guide you to your daughter.
I'm proud.
This is a contract.
Really?
Is that so?
Then, your parents also signed a contract
with this ghost.
I'm worried about that, too.
Let's go to the next place.
Please open the back door.
It's a little cold, but it's for your
daughter.
I'll do my best.
You are kind.
You pushed my back.
What is this person's contract?
What contract did you sign?
It's snowing.
It's a snowy mountain.
What is this?
This cake is no good.
This cake will be covered with snow.
This cake will be soaked in snow.
This is ASMR.
I opened the snow fairy.
This is the only thing I can open.
This is the worst door for my hand to
come out.
This is a trap.
This is a one-way street.
Can I go this way?
I'm not good at this.
This suddenly becomes difficult.
Please stop.
This is probably falling.
Please cross the middle.
This is a scary sound.
This sounds unpleasant, but I think it's
okay.
I think it's definitely not okay.
How is this?
Is this NOKIA?
What do you think, Nokia?
I don't think it's a good idea.
Can you help me?
Are you watching a video?
I think I've reached my goal.
It's falling.
What happened?
Is it okay because it's snowing?
I think it's okay.
It's shining.
Is it alive?
Yes, it's alive.
It was alive.
It's alive!
What is it?
It's a very strong body.
It's true.
Is this also thanks to the power of the
board?
What is the power of the board?
It looks like a normal board.
It's a very beautiful place.
Someone is waving their hand.
Is it yogurt?
It looks like blueberry.
It looks like a blueberry.
The way she waved her hand was cute.
I will imitate her.
I wave my hand like this to the fans who
came to see me at the time of MIGURI.
This is a cake.
Someone is coming.
Who is it?
Don't move.
Is that a cake?
It doesn't move.
I will not change it.
Someone is coming.
what?
I will do something about it.
Really?
If it's like this, I'm going to hit it.
Is it amazing?
I'm shaking too much.
Oh, it's back, it's back.
What?
The alarm clock.
What is that sound?
What is that sound now?
It's okay now.
What?
Did you do something?
Oh, you were intimidated by the sound of
my saxophone.
Oh, you can play the saxophone.
He'll attack me as soon as I make a
sound.
It's better not to move.
Don't move when you're close to me.
I understand.
Your last wish is to eat a birthday cake.
That's cute.
You are a little shy.
I'm not shy.
Birthday cakes are special when I was a
child.
Is your cake so delicious?
It's handmade.
I want to eat handmade cakes.
It's shining.
It's a light.
Blow the saxophone.
You are shaking too much.
This is not me.
I didn't do this.
This is a alarm clock.
This is dangerous.
Is it okay to go straight?
Is it okay to do it right away?
Why is that an alarm clock?
I'm waving my hand.
I saw it.
Does it open when I press it?
Is this a door?
Can I do this now?
Did the electricity go out?
This is dangerous.
Does this turn off the electricity?
I think so.
I go to these lights.
I turn off the lights.
I think it's better to have electricity,
but I've never used an alarm clock.
I've had a cell phone since I was in
elementary school.
I can see the bomb.
I can see the bomb inside the hut.
Can you see the inside of this room?
I can see the bomb.
What is this?
This is amazing.
It seems that the time has come to use
this.
What is this?
Is this the one from earlier?
Where did this come from?
This is coming here.
I will explain the strategy.
Why am I here?
I was just thinking about it.
If I use the door at this moment, I can
move anywhere in this snowy mountain.
I can do anything.
Then come with me.
I want you to take me to the entrance of
the snowy mountain with that.
That's right.
If I use this, my body will melt.
Is that still okay?
That's not good.
I will stop using it.
I can only use it a few more times.
I can only use it once.
That's right.
Then I'll stop it.
It's not a good story, but I'll explain
the strategy again today.
I'll play an instrument here and lure the
monster of the clock.
You have a bomb device and hide near it.
When the clock enters the hut, I'll give
you a signal.
When I hear the signal, I'll immediately
detonate the bomb device.
Then the hut will explode.
I escape through the teleportation door.
I'm going to escape through this door.
Only the monster of the clock will be
able to see through the cup.
I'm hiding outside the hut.
You're going to blow in the hut.
I want you to tell me about that.
What?
Will you do it to expose the danger of
your body?
I got it.
Are you okay?
I have a cake, but what should I do?
Now!
Oh!
Ah!
Ah! Oh!
Good!
The timing is coming out. What is it?
Time is going really fast.
It's like a monster that controls time.
Oh, that's not it.
The time is going back.
What happened?
How did this happen?
I can go back in time.
This is a lie.
I can't go back in time.
I can't do it again.
I saw a strange vision like a clock.
Is this the ability of the clock man?
If he dies, time will go back to the
cause of his death.
He is immortal.
That's right.
That's right, I think I did a good job,
so that's it.
Where did you go?
Don't leave me alone.
I got angry at a special event and
finished it.
I won't die.
I understand, I came from here, so I'll
go from here.
There are a lot of hands on the left and
right, alternately.
I found it!
I wonder if she has a name.
She's cute, isn't she?
I want her to care about me.
Oh!
A snowman.
I think something's going to happen here.
I can't get out of here.
All right.
What do you think?
I think it's the one in front of me.
She doesn't shake her hand.
I don't think there's anything here, but
I don't think so.
Is this the end? I feel like it's over.
Yes, it's already gone.
It was snowing before I knew it.
It's open, it's open, it's open, and I
think I should go here.
If I don't get out of here before the
clockman comes.
That's right, let's go.
Let's go to the park.
There's something good.
Ski?
Can you do it?
I've only been to a ski lesson once.
Left, right.
Where's the brake?
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't think I'll use the brake.
I don't think I'll ever use a cake.
But there are things like this.
I've done this before.
There's a Mario Kart stage like this.
If you jump here, it accelerates.
If you bend, the cake will go too.
If you bend a little too much, the cake
will...
Jump action now.
It accelerates properly.
Is this really chasing me?
Acceleration.
I can't play the piano, so I can't do
anything different with my right hand and
left hand, right?
That's amazing.
The snowman is watching our race.
I'm shaking my hand.
There are spectators on the left and
right.
It's dangerous!
It's in the middle.
This is dangerous.
I think I'm almost there.
Not yet.
Maybe a little more.
How is it?
A little more?
Not yet?
I think I'm almost there.
How is it?
It's like this when I hit it.
It bounced back.
It fell.
Where is this from?
Kind.
It's from here.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This is difficult.
You have to turn the cake in the opposite
direction.
I heard a man's voice.
Is this your father?
This is your father.
Let's go to your father.
As expected, let's go to your father.
I may not like this.
What should I do here?
Do you want me to do it?
I'll do it for now.
Damn it.
This way.
Is this a brake?
I told you not to use the brakes.
I forgot the existence of the brakes.
I'm scared.
I found out that I'm not good at racing
games.
I can do Mario Kart.
You can go to Mario Kart 8 Deluxe, right?
It's dangerous, dangerous, dangerous,
dangerous, dangerous, dangerous,
dangerous, dangerous, dangerous
What do you think?
Not yet?
Not yet.
After this, I think I'll be good at
multitasking.
I have a wide field of view now.
It's the same as basketball.
My coach told me this when I was playing
basketball.
I just remembered.
If you only look at one point, you won't
be able to see the surroundings.
You can't see the other team members, so
you have to look at the whole court in a
wide view and understand the whole thing.
The coach told me.
Don't accelerate.
Is there a reason why you should
accelerate?
I found an invincible elephant.
I did it.
How is it?
It's shining over there, so it looks like
a goal.
How is it?
Goal! Goal! Goal!
It's not a magatama, it's a floating
thing.
It's like a dead body.
What is this?
There is a machine.
What?
I was locked in.
That much?
What?
Oh!
What is it?
I used it.
I was able to do it.
Why?
It was all to bring that board here.
What power does this board have?
The daughter is a lie.
Wow!
This guy.
The cake is a lie.
There is a cake.
It is true that your daughter was in the
world of death.
But she is living in the old days.
Based on the story she heard before she
died.
I brought you here.
Death cannot enter that room.
I can't get into the board.
Hmm.
And you're the one who takes the cake.
Board.
That's not just protecting you from the
threat of the world of the dead.
I need that board.
I need a special power.
I need that.
Why?
If you solve it, my goal will be
achieved.
Then you're done for.
Well, then, the person who saved me is
already...
Hey!
I'm going to reincarnate.
Put the board on the machine.
Put it on the machine?
There is no exit, so I have to put it on
the machine.
What?
Where are you going?
Who are you?
I thought you were an ally.
You can't do that.
Really?
Who is an ally?
Oh, it's a friend!
It's a friend!
It's cute.
My father is a patissier.
The cake my father makes is the most
delicious in the world.
I have a good daughter.
I was born with a cake.
Please welcome me.
I will come back from school with a super
special class.
It's cute.
I have a cute daughter.
I was promised to eat a cake.
I remember that.
I want to go see her.
I want to go to the store, but I'm sure
the one I saw earlier is lying.
I'm sure my daughter is still waiting
outside.
I didn't see the cake here.
There is a door here.
There is no one here.
This is dangerous.
The people who were outside the store
were originally humans.
She's a human being, isn't she?
Oh!
Home!
Daddy's waiting here for my daughter to
come home!
The cake I made!
Oh!
Ping pong!
What is it?
Ah!
Are you sure it's in your house?
Is that cake for your daughter?
Is that so?
Actually, I have something to tell you
about my daughter.
It's very difficult to say, but...
My daughter had a car accident on the way
home from school.
I was dragged into the hospital.
I see.
I was immediately transferred to the
hospital.
I had to go through a lot of treatment.
I was turned into a school of death.
I dropped the cake.
I see.
My daughter died on her birthday.
It's a button.
What?
The daruma fell.
Isn't it?
I wonder if it's because of the light
over there that I'm worried that it's
shaking.
Do, Re, Mi, Fa, Sol, La, Si, Do.
I wonder if I have to go around this.
There is a wall here.
Can I go from either side?
I can't see it if I look sideways.
It's dark and I can't see it.
I think it's this way.
Is it this way?
Is it the right way?
This is a scary system.
There is still nothing here.
There is a wall here.
Is it a little further back?
I think I can go straight if I go to the
bottom of the light and go straight, but
I wonder if I can go a little more, but I
have a cake, but I have a cake, but I
have a cake, but I have a cake,
I heard this while my house was in a
mess.
This is the person I talked to earlier.
This is NOKIWA.
You are there.
You were sad about your daughter.
Your daughter needs your help now.
Your daughter's soul is trapped in the
world of the dead.
If you leave it as it is, your daughter
will become a terrible monster.
You are the only one who can prevent
that.
PAPA, will you listen to me?
I can't believe this is happening in
reality, but if it's for my daughter, it
's going to happen, isn't it?
I say it myself, but it's often like
this.
Don't use difficult words.
Well, first of all, go to the shrine and
cut the tree.
If you cut the tree into a board, I see.
I see, I see.
It's on the TV screen.
Dig a mark.
It will protect you in the world of the
dead.
It's a sacred tree in the shrine.
One more thing.
I have an important job.
Make a cake for my daughter.
I met her here.
I see.
This is the board I made.
What is this?
This is the first part.
Something...
Well...
Oh!
Hmm?
He's teaching me!
What is it?
Hahaha
This window...
It's like the road we saw earlier...
Well...
Um...
Blueberry-chan was there...
Oh!
What?
Hahaha
That convenient?
What?
I was there when I looked sideways.
I'll drop it at a place that has nothing
to do with it at all.
I just tried to see that girl again.
This is the only place I've been to, but
there's really a place like this, isn't
there?
There it is.
Is there that much?
Is there that much of a button?
It's dangerous.
There it is.
Is this stage this girl?
Can I pass through?
I went somewhere.
Where's the other one?
Here?
Around here?
Is it the other way around?
Did I go this way?
Did I not go this way?
It's difficult.
I think I went this way.
Did I go up here too?
It's pitch black.
But I can see something.
It's the same as the first time.
I was surprised.
I want to see my daughter soon.
Here?
I have to eat the cake my dad made for
me.
How is it?
Cake?
Oh, there it is.
Is it for my daughter?
I'm so happy.
I've prepared a cake for my daughter.
I can't see the picture, so I have to
believe I have it.
I have no choice but to do it.
Before I go to the world of the dead, I
first make a contract.
Oh, this is it.
Use that board for the contract.
Hold the board firmly with both hands.
If you let go of the board, you will lose
your defense power.
Okay, let's get started.
I got it.
This is the world of the dead.
The purpose is to deliver the cake to the
daughter.
I am the guide.
When this person achieves the purpose, I
will take the board with the power of my
father.
Okay.
Now the contract is finalized.
As long as the contract is valid, you
will not be able to use it, but the
moment it is decided that the contract
will not be fulfilled, the power of the
board will be lost.
For example, if the cake goes bad due to
some accident, you will not be able to
use it.
I know why you die when you drop the
cake.
It means that you will die if you don't
fulfill the contract.
I know why you will die if you drop the
cake.
No matter what happens, protect the cake.
The world of the dead is a terrifying
place.
Prepare yourself and challenge it.
I see.
If I give the cake to my dad, he will get
the board.
Why did he try to steal it?
Is he really not here?
Oh, what?
Wow!
Wow, there are a lot of big armadillos.
It's like a butterfly knot.
This is the hand that comes out when the
game is over.
From the side like this.
It's KON.
It's amazing.
Aki is here.
He's wearing a hat.
Isn't this a girl?
Isn't this a special edition?
This is my daughter's hat I gave her on
her birthday last year.
She's wearing it.
She's going to play for me.
Hang in there.
If you don't, you'll be eaten.
What?
No way.
I'll just think about running away.
Oh, you forgot.
I have a cake.
I see.
I'll prepare a escape route.
That's right, I said I was a monster just
now, I'm not a monster, I'm a monster, I
'm a monster, I'm a monster, I'm a
monster, I'm a monster, I'm a monster, I
monster, I'm a monster, I'm a monster
I've started to absorb everything.
Even the most powerful monsters in this
world.
And I'm using the ability of the monsters
I've absorbed to make my own.
Oh!
There's a lot of Jujutsu Kaisen coming
out.
It's like Geto-san's ability.
That's amazing. That's strong.
The world of the dead is in chaos.
The connections between the spaces are
also scattered.
What should I do?
Should I tell this to Keikyo?
Should I tell Kyotoku about this?
Or should I tell him that I met him in
the world of the dead a little while ago?
A child of a certain parent has become a
monster.
It's the end of that parent and child.
I don't want to see that again.
That's right.
He decided to play a play.
I see, it was a play.
He is kind.
I'm glad he wasn't deceived.
It's not like I was fooled.
He's too kind, isn't he?
You noticed it for me, didn't you?
You were convinced by that hat, weren't
you?
That you were a monster.
I didn't make it in time.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
I lied to you.
I really didn't want to talk to you.
I'm sorry.
No matter what I say, it's just an
excuse.
That's all I can say.
No, that's not true.
Forgive me.
Will you give it to me?
Yeah.
Cute.
Sorry.
Thank you.
What should I do from now on?
You're right.
Even just a cake.
I have an idea.
What should I do from now on?
Oh.
Oh, wow.
My body was good from the time I was
born.
Oh, it's about your backbone.
That's what I thought when I came to my
life.
But I can't do it.
I can't say that singing is good at
singing.
I've never even touched a instrument.
I see.
I can't be like that.
That's what I decided.
It's a bad habit from my childhood.
And I tell myself.
It's not a big deal anyway.
That made me feel better.
I was protecting myself like that.
That's how I've always been protecting
myself.
I'm proud of you, I'm proud of you.
I've overcome it well.
I have a surgery.
And that's the end of my life.
It's my death anniversary.
The more my parents die, the farther I
go.
At that time, my consciousness was cut
off for just a moment.
A certain thought crossed my mind.
Was this good for my life?
Is this the end of my life?
I couldn't do anything I wanted to do.
And I woke up in the world of the dead.
Until the last moment.
What is this?
It's the same as the beginning.
I'm waiting at the snowy mountain.
Who is waiting for me?
I'm hoping for you to go somewhere.
I'm waiting for you.
I'm going.
I think the number of paintings has
increased.
There is also a painting called SAKURA at
the beginning.
I came back.
There are a lot of pictures of flowers.
She is waving her hand.
Hello.
It's been a long time since I've seen
you.
She is very humble.
If you get close to her, she will
disappear.
She is cute.
That girl is cute.
How far should I go?
I feel like I'm repeating the same path
over and over again.
I'm in danger.
You are the first person on the stage.
Yes, I was eaten.
But.
She is my daughter.
She is strong.
I see.
Did you call her?
No, I didn't call her.
It was grass.
I wanted to see her so much that I could
see the screen.
I thought I was going to lose my hand,
but I can't see it.
Oh, my daughter.
Can I get through?
I did it!
Oh, no!
Cake, cake, cake first.
Can I get in?
Are you being chased?
Oh, no!
Who is it?
The first person came.
There was a first person who came here.
There was a person who came to this place
for the first time.
I feel like this is the last time.
I run and run away.
This will definitely come, right?
Wait a minute.
Is it okay to go straight?
Will something come?
The scenery around here is like that.
This is the same place.
I can't leave such a narrow road.
The door won't open.
It's open.
Here.
Yes.
It's here.
It's snowing.
What is this?
This is amazing.
This is very big.
This is a cake.
I didn't see the cake.
This is dangerous.
This is a big girl.
This has grown.
What should I do?
Will he remember me?
Daddy, I'm skiing.
Oh, there he is!
He's here!
Oh, this is a little...
Not cute.
Oh, I said it's not cute.
That's it.
It's a little...
It's not adorable.
Oh, it's dangerous!
Dangerous!
I feel like I'm getting better at this.
Ugh!
In the middle.
Like this.
Oh, it's dangerous!
How is it?
Do you still ski here?
Oh, I found it.
Are you waiting for me?
Look, I'm back.
I'm back.
Do you want to eat?
That's great.
It's dangerous.
My friend is here.
What should I do with the contract?
If you deliver the cake, you want this
board, right?
Can I make it come back to life?
Should I do it here?
It swallowed the bomb.
The daughter...
It's a cake.
What will happen?
It exploded.
The daughter...
Oh, I see.
I ate the watch monster earlier.
Time goes back.
I see.
How far did it go back?
It's open!
Where did it go?
Is my daughter here?
How is it?
It was here before I became a monster.
It's wearing a hat.
I brought you a cake.
Your face is so cute.
I'm surprised.
It's cute.
You are so cute!
You did it! We won the bet!
Dad, it was hard to come all the way
here, wasn't it?
It was hard.
I'm happy to see you one last time.
My daughter!
Let's go home together.
Thank you for bringing the cake all the
way here.
I ate it.
How is it? How is it? Is it good?
After all, I love the cake my dad makes
the most in the world.
I like it the most in the world.
It's cute.
I feel very happy when I eat it.
I want everyone around the world to eat
my cake.
This is a patissier.
Everyone will feel happy when they eat
this.
Everyone will cheer up and do their best
tomorrow.
This is a kind child.
This is a good child.
I ate it all.
This is the last bite.
If I eat it, this time will end.
Father, I'm scared to disappear.
That's right.
Don't disappear.
I came to see you.
But I'm more scared to be a monster.
That's true.
So I have to be brave.
I have to get out of here.
It's like my father came to me.
What should I do?
Do you want to eat?
I'm glad my father was there at the end.
I'm glad I was able to make my daughter
say it at the end.
Thank you, father.
My daughter is too good.
Please tell me.
My daughter is gone.
The child is gone.
The child is crying and his vision is
blurred.
You did a good job.
You really did a good job.
This is a kind ending.
This was the best ending for that child.
So now you can cry as much as you want.
You can cry.
Now that the contract has been fulfilled,
we will say goodbye.
What will happen to you?
I'll send you back to me with this board
you brought.
You're going to send me back?
If you've overcome the world of the dead,
you'll be able to face any difficulties
from now on.
See you.
What about you?
You're not going to come to this world
again.
You're going to send me back, aren't you?
What?
Can I be an animal?
Thank you, but I'm worried about you too.
Oh, can you hear me?
Yes, it's a little noisy, but it seems to
be working.
Hello everyone in the world.
I'm sorry that I suddenly jacked up about
60% of the video devices that exist all
over the world.
It's amazing.
Let's stop the soccer broadcast and the
wild news for now and listen to a song.
Let's have you listen to the music.
Hmm, that kind of use is amazing.
I can do anything.
There is a lot of trouble in implementing
this stage today.
I was impressed by the perverted person
who had the opportunity.
Well, I don't care about the gossip.
It's my first and last sunny stage.
Oh, that's right.
I wanted to do that.
Sorry, but I won't skip it.
Listen carefully.
Music start.
It's what I wanted to do.
That's right.
I'm singing.
I'm the only performer.
I'm the only one who does that part.
That's amazing.
That's really good.
When we parted ways, I said,
You are?
I see.
Thank you for bringing me a cake.
Thank you very much.
Don't drop the cake.
This is a good game.
I'm back.
I thought it was a scary horror game that
surprised me, but the story was
interesting and I was chased by a smile.
What is this game? Thank you very much.
It was fun. It was a little difficult,
but I'm not good at multitasking, but it
was fun and it was a game that warmed my
heart.
It was a game that made me want to play
it again.
I was hoping that the main character
would become a worldwide patissier.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
How was everyone?
If you like it, please play it.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to the channel and give
it a high rating.
See you.